{
    "id": "abc0990116104ceab8d264ded6b35291",
    "title": "Combine using unless",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "02016e2705e8498998052aad655313bd",
            "title": "Unless Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Unless you work hard, you ...................................... win.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "cannot"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Unless the boys work hard, they .......................................... fail.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "won't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Unless you .......................................... early, you will get stuck in the traffic.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "start",
                        "started",
                        "don't start"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Unless you hire a taxi, you .............................................. miss the train.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "won't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": ".............................................. you obey my orders, you will be dismissed.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Unless",
                        "If"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Unless you take an umbrella, you ........................................ get wet.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "won't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Unless you work hard, you ........................................... pass the examination.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "won't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Unless we receive enough rain, there ............................................. be a shortage of electricity.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "won't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Unless Gopal ........................................... a good doctor his condition may get worse.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "doesn't consult",
                        "consults"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Unless they come early, they ............................................... get the tickets.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "won't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}